

# Contact

#### **Phone**

+375 33 628-65-38

#### **Email**

buladzislau@gmail.com

#### **Address**

Ostrovec, Belarus









# **Education**

2023

React / Redux / TS
IT-INCUBATOR

2022

HTML / CSS / JS / TS / React RS SCHOOL

2013-2018

**Bachelor of Engineering**Belarusian National Technical University

# **Expertise**

- React / Redux
- Javascript / TypeScript
- HTML / CSS / SCSS
- RestAPI / Axios
- GIT / Github
- TDD / Jest / Storybook

# Languages

English - Intermediate (B1)

Russian - Native

# Vladislav Belyaev

Frontend Developer

# **About me**

I'm a Frontend Developer with more than 1.5 year of experience creating SPA using React, Redux, TypeScript and JavaScript. I'm currently studying React and Redux deeper. In free time I like to solve tasks on Codewars and improve my English skills. I'm open for new opportunities and open to relocating Europe.

# **Experience**

2022 - present (1.5 year) part-time | Project Work

**Frontend Developer** 

# **TODO LIST**

TODO LIST is an application where you can create list of tasks you should to do.

Stack: React / Redux / Typescript / Javascript / MaterialUI / Axios / React-Router-dom

#### **SOCIAL NETWORK**

This is an analogue of any social network that you know (VK, Facebook)
Stack: React / Redux / Typescript / Javascript / Axios / React Hook
Form / React-Router-dom

### **TASK MANAGER (teamwork)**

We've created an application, which you can help to manage your project, similar to the Jira application.

Stack: React / Redux / Typescript / Axios / MaterialUI / React Hook Form / React-Router-dom / i18next

### RS LANG (teamwork)

We've created an analogue of the learning platform Lingualeo.

Stack: Typescript / JavaScript / HTML / SCSS / RestAPI / ESLint / Webpack

### **ASYNC RACE**

Async Race is an application where you start a race and the cars start moving, there will be only 1 winner. During the race, any machine can break down. The server decides which machine to break down .

Stack: Typescript / JavaScript / HTML / SCSS / RestAPI / ESLint / Webpack

# 2018 - present (5 years)

full-time | Belarusian Nuclear Power Plant

## **Turbine equipment operator**

Work with technical documentation and production schemes.

Check for compliance with production schemes, make changes.

Control of works performance and quality.

Commissioning of the facility.